Jhal Hello, welcome to the
next episode of Learn German in Hindi. Last time
we learned the German alphabets, today we will
learn only 18 words and all the German numbers, we will
start with the words, so as we said we are going to
learn not only 18 words, so the
first 13 of them we will
learn for one year, we will learn that now, so the
first one is 0, that is Nurul, now see,
in the last episode we had bad, once rotated,
its treatment will be permanent, no
Nul, after that lines,
Suhaye cracks, Fever, Chunnu,
Awax, A river
of nine, Train, Value, Soil,
now once again we will see
lines, S Y, Dry Fruit Sim,
this time,
Thursday no. 7, Glad Soil, we had
said that we will learn only 18 more and
all the numbers will come, but we already learned that
only your number will come, then how to proceed,
it is very easy, how we see, from
now on they are in 1919 and you
just add less than that, from 10 to 14 it becomes only,
that is
not suitable, then 90, then you will see  So from
13 to 19 we did not learn anything, we just kept on putting
fences, you got 13 to 19 free,
now we will learn a new word on the 14th, gambling on the face also from the
solution of the issue, as we said last time, there are
some areas, it is
called join addict, but we are learning hop tricks,
so we will say this lineage, okay,
so we learned the nak, right now we know 1 to
20, now we will learn 30, 40, 50, 60, 70, 80, 90,
remember how you did it in English, for 30, 40, 15, 16,
you put p in the end in mind, we will put
more easy with at the end, what will we put, jade
pimp, progressivism, so 30 is dry fish
four, if it is clear then 40, happy, jis film
juice, English, Vishakh, special nine, so if you get
30, then you got the marks, okay, okay,
and now we will learn three new words,
net, they are zoological, right
town and students through, strong
cats, one means million,
like Hindi, lakh ka crisis is not there in the channel,
not all European languages.  Yes, it
is clear to everyone, Honda Tau Judgement Million,
so now see what all I know, I know from 1 to
20, I know 30 40 50 60
70 80 90, I am handed over to me, I know thousand, I get it,
what do I not know, I do
not know 21 22 23 24 ride and here
again our Hindi story
because if you see what is 21 22 23
called in English, then 13, so if
you see here, first the tenth position comes
20 30 and then the tenth position, so
see in Hindi, how do you do it, 21 22 23,
so what did you take first, which position did you take first,
I do the same in Hindi, in German also, but
at least in Hindi you made its Sunny,
one, I made 22, where there is
also this from it, there is one more German, I am
frustrated, Kund, Kund, meaning and 120 Janmat
like that
one  And B-2 and 20 320 like this we will go I Kunai Na ...  It
goes once and then you go to 99,
so you are just adding it, for
example, if you have to say 2222 2222, then
what are you doing, you are saying two different things,
200 crore is simple, once you add up to 100, then
whatever
number after that, it is very simple, everyone has
understood now,
if you want to revise it, then I will
tell you a very easy trick, if you will do that
trick, then in two days you will get
all the German numbers, so what is that,
in German you call the clock and there you will get the
foot and how do you tell the time, 9:30,
so 9:30 9:30, then you will tell how it is made in German,
first the hour, then those people or minutes,
nine from the date and David, if it is 10:45, then it will come
close to 3000, tell the time,
when in the whole day when Bigg Boss
tells his time
that it is 01:36, come and do this for two
days, you will start getting all the German numbers
Okay, so let's take a very review
and today we submit the day nowadays so
like we learned from zero to 12 we will have to remember
online viagra be careful in the
given you nine sad song 1319 put crush put
me new year's hassle then 3 to
90 what will you do put vulture capital
subject na inch three new words them
zoom and 21 22 23 24 one more thing like Hindi
so also three pieces research and district
and session judge and when there are big numbers then
we break them on our side 3333
and strong terms and dry beautiful driver
British I hope you all
understood it easily less than German numbers
in the next lesson we will see two most
important works to have you also and give your
introduction so see you
in the next episode thank you it happened